(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-04T03:24:11.558724",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi!
関西 関東 西 東
Kansai, Kanto, West, East,
北 南 チーム友達
North, South, Team Tomodachi!
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
チーム チーム チーム友達
Team, team, Team Tomodachi!
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi!
お好み焼き 食う鶴橋
Eating okonomiyaki in Tsuruhashi,
腹いっぱい 飯は美味い
full belly, the food is delicious.
一人じゃ寂しいし 電話きたり
It's lonely all by myself, getting calls,
かけ直したあとすぐ行く 会いに
right after calling back, going straight to meet up.
T-E-A-M T-O-M-O D-A-C-H-I
チーム友達 混ざり合い
Team Tomodachi, mixing together,
契り交わし 飲んでる酒
pledging vows, drinking sake.
契り 契り
Vow, vow
契ろう 契ろう
Let's vow, let's vow
契り 契り
Vow, vow
契ろう 契ろう
Let's vow, let's vow
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi!
関西 関東 西 東
Kansai, Kanto, West, East,
北 南 チーム友達
North, South, Team Tomodachi!
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
チーム チーム チーム友達
Team, team, Team Tomodachi!
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi!
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
ふふっ
Hehe.
You know, come to think of it, it's been two years since we broke out of the cell, huh?
Yeah! Time goes by fast.
Yeah, we've been through a lot, right?
Huh? What?
Hey, guys!
What's that over there? No way!
Huh?
Attention. Justice, Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame,
initiating final warning protocol.
Five escapees detected from the cell.
Repeat, five escapees detected from the cell.
Targets are as follows:
The Demon of Sound, Nerissa Ravencroft.
The Jewel of Emotions, Koseki Bijou.
The Fluffy One, Fuwawa Abyssgard.
The Fuzzy One, Mococo Abyssgard.
The Archiver, Shiori Novella.
All units, apprehend the Advent members immediately.
Oh no! No way! No!
Oh no, we're in trouble! Is it the police?
Oh my god, they're catching us! They're catching me!
Oh my gosh, we're actually caught! What are we gonna do?
No way, what should we do? What should we do?!
Oh, what should we do?
Wait, guys, think. There's got to be a solution for this, right?
Piggyback ride! Come on!
Oh! Piggyback ride! Go go go! No!
Okay, maybe not that one.
There has to be something though, like a Plan B or something we can do.
Bwahaha! Struggling already?
Ah! What? Oh my god! What are you doing here?
You finally showed your face, huh? Yeah!
Ask nicely enough, and maybe I'll save your skins.
Oh, I'll punch you forever and ever. Come on!
Wait, um, here. I have a solution.
Huh? Oh? Wow! No way! Please, help us, Pokey!
Hmph! I don't hate that.
If you manage to pass the little trial I've cooked up for you,
I'll whisk you away to a whole other realm...
One where your pesky pursuers can't reach you!
I mean, I guess that's our only option, huh? I guess so.
Oh well, guess we will do it.
Alright. I've prepared something special. Arise, my go-karts!
Go-karts? Really? Nice! Whoa! Yay!
What if we don't have a license?
What's with all the Moai statues and stuff?
Yeah, interesting! I like that.
See this course? Time to tackle the "Go-Kart Escape Challenge"!
Oh, escape? Escape go-karting? Okay!
Yes, that's right. Take it from here, ankle-biter.
Who are you talking to, huh? Who are you talking to? Ankle-biter?
Yeah, calm down there. Actually, alright, team!
Game rules are incoming, so make sure you better listen, okay?
Okay! Okay! Wait, one second.
Shiori, Shiori, can I get...? Thank you.
Yah!
Oh, nice! Wait, Bijou, how do you know the game rules? Isn't like... huh?
It's the glasses. That's how she knows. Oh, the glasses!
Rule 1! Survive 2 laps with zombies on your tail!
Zombies?! Where? Remember last year we beat up zombies?
Well, one of them went on a path to revenge, and now it's going to run after you.
Oh, okay. Fun.
Rule 2! Collect items for bonus points, but watch out because there will be some that deduct points too!
Oh no! Deduct points?
And then, Rule 3 is victory is ours if we all get 30 points total. Easy, right?
30 points? 30 points? We can do that. Yeah.
Alright, and now I will explain the course items.
I must run.
You must run? Yeah, I must run.
She must be with her people. Go. I'm gonna live out my dreams while there's a track here. Just explain, ignore me, ignore me.
Okay, mhm. Alright, so make sure you're listening.
There are... oh, she's fast. There are crystals on the field. Like the Bijou crystal over there.
And two more over there, they are gacha.
Oh!
You either gain points or lose points based on...
...but you don't know, so it's a risk every time. Yeah.
And then there is the big Moai!
The big Moai!
It will block your path.
Woah! It is minus 20 points...
...if you hit it, so don't hit it.
Don't hit it. Don't hit it. And then, the Pebble!
The Pebble?
I have kidnapped one of my Pebbles to use as a sacrifice. If you hit it...
...minus 5 points, but you know what? I don't think they'd mind if you hit it, to be honest.
Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah, it is what it is.
And the items will change...
...depending on your first lap or second lap. You're doing two laps.
Two laps. Alright.
There are too many. You can run another two laps?
Yeah. Yeah, are you okay? Yeah, I'm great.
I guess time to show you how it's done.
Sure. Go on, go on.
Alright, first lap. Show us how to do it.
I'm ready.
3, 2, 1...
Go!
Oh, first lap, first lap, first lap.
She got a crystal, she made it. Second crystal.
Oh, she's so fast.
Oh, zombie's spinning. Zombie!
Second lap, let's go, let's go!
Another crystal. She hit another one.
Oh, zombie! Zombie! Watch out!
Oh, the Pebble! Pebble!
No, she hit it!
Yeah, she made it!
I think you got a bit of bad luck with that crystal at the end.
Oh...
It's okay, that was a pretty good run. You did so fast.
You were so fast.
Oh, you almost hit the zombie but you're okay. You're okay.
You didn't die. How many points did I get? How many points?
That's a good question. How many points did you get?
How many points did I get?
I think you got 1 point.
What? 1 point? After all that?
Did I have bad gacha luck?
No, it's a group effort, we can still get points.
Yeah, I can still get points. One. One is great.
We can let the pro do all the work for you, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Pro? Who, me?
Yeah, yeah. It's up to you guys.
Okay, next up is Shiori!
Oh, show us how it's done, our fearless leader.
I have a plan.
What's your plan?
You'll figure it out when I say plan.
Okay. Good luck, Shiori!
あの、あの、ゾンビは避けてどうぞ。
Um, um, please avoid the zombies.
Eh? What? What?
Okay, I see. I see.
3, 2, 1... Let's go!
Oh, yeah, that's what I thought. Come on, let's go, let's go!
Oh, she hit it! Oh, no!
Oh, she got a crystal. Run, run, run!
Oh, she got a minus. No!
Oh, zombie's spinning. Zombie!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like driving in New York!
Oh, she got a crystal! Wow!
You got another one! Go, go, go!
Oh, oh, oh, she hit a Pebble!
No, she got a minus!
You didn't catch him, but you sure gave him a run for his money.
I don't care about the points, I just want to run them over.
Understandable. Oh, you did great.
It's okay, Shiori, did you like it? Yes.
Oh, 3 points! 3 points!
I got 3 points. That's it, I'm running you over.
That's 2 more points than Bijou. That was pretty good.
Yeah, that's better than 1.
So we have... we have 4? All right, it's up to Fuwawa!
Do you think you can do it?
I will get more than 1 point. You can do it. I know you can do it.
I'm pretty sure the zombie is not going to run away anymore, so...
Yeah, I think it's tired.
It's up to you, you got to outrun the zombie.
You're the best, Fuwawa! You can do it!
3, 2, 1...
Go!
Oh, no! She's so fast!
You're kind of close. What do you mean?
I want to go fast. Oh, she's a very safe driver.
She got the crystal. There is a zombie, watch out.
So slow! So slow!
Go, go, go!
Watch out! Fire!
Oh no! My points!
My crystal! It's okay, it's okay!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Faster! Faster! Go, go!
Oh, it's just so slow this time!
Turn! Turn! Ruby, ruby!
Nice! Five points!
Watch out, the zombie is coming!
Go! Go! Go!
Second lap! Second lap!
Is it still the first lap? No, second lap!
Go, go, go! Ruby, ruby!
Nice! Five points!
Watch out for the giant head!
Go! Go! Oh my god!
Turn! Turn! Watch out!
Oh, no! The fire!
No! Finish line!
Fuwawa! You did it!
I guess speed isn't that important, but the points are!
Fuwawa, I think you did really well!
And so far, you are our top performer today with...
18 points!
18?! Wow, Fuwawa!
Wait, isn't it 14?
What was the math? 17? 18?
14, 18! Because you lost three, and you got one...
So yeah, 18!
No, no, we got 18 points. Okay, next is Mococo!
Mococo, go! All the points, okay? Count on me!
Mococo! You got this, Mococo!
Okay, countdown!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Go, Mococo, go!
Oh, it's so slow! It's a slow burn!
Nice! Crystal!
Yay, five points!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Fire!
Watch out, watch out! No!
The crystal! Get it!
Oh my god! Mococo, turn!
Go, go, go! Crystal, crystal!
Turn, turn! Nice, nice!
Watch out, the zombie is coming!
Go, Mococo! Almost there!
Finish line! Yay!
How did I do? How did I do?
Mococo, you did really great!
I think with you, we have enough points!
Yeah, you got 12 points!
12 points! Plus 18, that's...
That's 30 points!
Mococo, high five! High five!
Yay!
Wait, can you get negative points?
You can get negative points? Oh no...
If Shiori gets negative points, she'll ruin it!
No, she won't! I believe in Shiori!
I have a driver's license, so I'm not worried about this at all.
Driver's license?! Oh wow!
But there are zombies here!
I'm not scared of zombies.
Okay, 3, 2, 1, Go!
Go, Shiori!
A slow start... Yeah, so slow!
Crystal! Nice!
Oh, fire! -3 points!
Watch out for the zombie!
Turn, Shiori, turn!
Crystal! Get the crystal!
Nice! Go, go, go!
Second lap! Watch out!
Crystal! Get the crystal!
Nice! Look at her go!
Almost there! Almost there!
And fire again! -3 points!
Oh no! But she's almost at the finish!
Finish! Yay!
I don't know if that went well...
But I think I probably did better than you guys!
Did you get negative points? I only spun out three times!
What are my points?
You got...
9 points!
9 points! Yay!
That means our total points is 39!
39 points! We did it!
We passed! Yay!
Pokey, we did it! We got the points!
So, what do you say, Pokey?
Do we get our deal?
[Pokey] Not bad!
[Pokey] As promised, interdimensional travel! All aboard!
[Pokey] Get in and go!
Wow, what a ride! But let's crash it!
No, I have a better idea.
What idea?
Let's make a music video!
Ah!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy
I can't get enough
Free as a bird, no limit
Haven't you heard? I'm fearless
Get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me...
be your diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shakin' up all the crowd
Making some noise when I'm not allowed
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my every whim
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Now pay attention, please
'Cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc
How do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings
I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
Gonna start the rave, when I misbehave, take center stage
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken; the rules can all be broken
I'm runnin' on a rampage
The world is a blank page
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name!
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands
But they don't understand
That I'm a star in the making, awaking and taking a bow
Tell me how you like me now
Come and watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me -
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control
Ready? You've got to free your mind
Leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous
The chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning, it's our genesis!
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings
I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Yeah! You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Oh my god!
We're on the beach!
We're actually here!
Oh my gosh, we actually have swimsuits!
Wait, this is so cute!
No way, look at this!
This is amazing!
We look so good!
Oh, this is us!
Yeah, I like it. It feels nice and breathable.
I want to see everyone close up, though. This is our first time wearing something like this, so...
Bijou!
Why don't you show off what you've got?
Okay, me first, okay?
What are you looking at, huh? What are you looking at?
Fine, you can look a little bit, okay?
Okay, here we go. This is my skirt. Do you like this skirt?
Oh, it's so vibrant!
You're like highlighters!
Wow!
Kira-kira! I'm going to blind you!
Oh, my eyes! It's too bright!
It's so sparkly!
Fuwawa, take over!
Go, go!
This is kind of my first bathing suit, but...
I...
What do you think?
But still so cozy and warm!
Bau bau!
Oh, Fuwawa!
Fuwawa!
Yeah! Ah, Shiori! Come here!
Shiori's, Shiori's, oh! Shiori's...
At your service!
And look at my little ribbon!
Cute! / Oh!
Mococo-chan!
Mococo-chan, Mococo-chan!
Okay, you can do this, Mococo-chan!
Bau bau!
I...
Yeah! Mococo-chan, you can do it!
Does it suit me? Do I look cute?
Look at those cute shorts!
Hi! Hi! / She's so cute!
Ah! Oh!
Mococo-chan!
Last but not least...
There's something a bit special on this outfit...
...don't you think? If you go down...
Oh, there it is! There it is!
Whoa!
Don't look there too much, but if you come up...
...you can see my waist...
...and my top.
Armpits!
Yes, the pits!
But, I see something strange off in the distance.
Just wait, let me go see.
What is it? / Oh!
It's a selfie stick!
Everyone, get behind me!
Let's take a picture together!
Smile! / Yeah!
Why is it so tall?
Oh! / Fuwawa!
Oh, that helps! / Whoa!
Cheese!
Oh, wait. Ah...
There's something down there in the sand.
What is that? / I think that's an Adventurer.
Oh! / Wow!
Ah! / Oh! What is that?
Careful!
Yeah! / Cute!
Okay, uh...
Let's go to the water! / Yeah!
Don't drown, okay? / Aww!
Running in slow-mo!
Let's just keep running on the beach.
I wanna catch you, Fuwawa! / Catch me!
Run!
I'm going to put this thing down, okay?
My arm is getting tired.
Selfie arm tired?
Yeah, selfie arm is losing it.
Thank you for being the selfie stick person.
Oh my gosh! It's Pokey! / What? Pokey!
[Pokey]: Hey now! Save the beach party for later!
[Pokey]: Sandcastles later, survival now!
They already detected your dimension jump.
I thought we were supposed to be safe here.
Yeah! What are we supposed to do?
We just got our swimsuits!
[Pokey]: This is Justice we're dealing with!
Expect the unexpected!
Eh...
What should we do next, then?
Will we have to run forever?
[Pokey]: Don't panic, I have a plan.
[Pokey]: Prove your bonds in the next trial,
and I may assist you.
The power of friendship? Nakama power?
Well, this is the beach episode!
We have to do this!
[Pokey]: Good. Something's been arranged.
Look down! A & B!
A and B? What are you talking about?
That's so lame! A! B!
[Pokey]: C-Can it! Silence!
[Pokey]: To confirm your bonds,
you'll take on "Master of Advent."
What is that? / Oh...
[Pokey]: The rules are simple! Each participant
will be asked a two-option question...
[Pokey]: ...related to Advent. You guys are
Team Tomodachi, so it should be pretty easy...
Yeah! No doubt!
We know everything about Advent!
[Pokey]: Exactly. But incorrect answers mean...
your bonds are weak, so I prepared a penalty game!
Penalty?! Penalty game?!
I didn't consent to this!
[Pokey]: Yeah, a penalty game. Now, goth girl, take over.
Anyway, I think that we're going to get
one question, two answers...
...but only one is right.
And if you get it wrong, unfortunately,
I think you're going to get muddied.
Oh! Muddy?! / What?!
I don't wanna get muddy in this thing!
So muddy...
So, when you make your answer,
I want you to hop there, okay?
Oh! Hop, hop, hop!
Okay, I'll go first as an example.
Number one! Which would Shiori rather be?
A vampire, A...
...or a werewolf, for B?
On the count of three, okay?
Three... Two...
One, go!
Werewolf! Werewolf!
Why werewolf?
I don't want to drink blood. What am I, stupid?
Oh, that's unexpected.
Yeah, I seriously thought you were going to say vampire.
No. You got that dog in you?
She literally has that dog in her, yeah.
I literally have the dog in me, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Well, we're already wet anyway.
No, no!
Yay! Get her!
Spray her! Spray her!
Oh, no! Why did I get dirty?
Oh, god.
No! Why did I get dirty?
Go! Go wash yourself!
Wash it! Yuck!
You too. I'm watching you.
Well, you got us all wet, Shiori. Are you happy?
Not yet.
All right. Next one, how about Mococo?
Moco-chan! My turn, my turn!
Okay, wow! Here I go!
Um, at the beach, would I rather collect seashells, A...
...or, um, how was it? Make sandcastles, B.
Okay? Figure out. Ready?
Okay, jump on three. Okay.
Three, two, one!
Which one?
I can't remember.
This was seashells, and this was sandcastles.
Shiori's getting dirty! Huh?
Yeah! It's Shiori! No, I thought you wanted this one!
I made a mistake!
I'd rather collect seashells, but I jumped this way. So that means this way is right!
This way!
This is not fair. Moco-chan, talk!
Yes, yes! Go, go, go!
Ah, my eyes! Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
All right.
Shiori's safe now. Yeah, for now. For now. Yeah! Okay, I had fun.
That was so mean! Seriously.
It was a game of chance, sister. But who's next? Okay.
Okay! Here I am. I don't get to get dirty this time, right? Yeah.
Okay! My question!
Do I prefer long-haired cats or short-haired cats?
Okay, jump on countdown. Here we go!
Three, two, one!
No way!
What do you mean you prefer short-haired? You literally have one!
It's so easy! This is a trick question! It's so obvious!
You're so mean to me!
Get her! Get her! Okay, here it goes!
Oh, my god!
Bae, help! Ah, my eyes!
Oh, god.
Ah, that feels nice. Yeah?
Well, it's going to be your turn next. Ah, my turn?
Nerissa, come back!
I don't want to play this game anymore! But you have to!
Okay, is it Bijou's turn now? It's Bijou's turn! Bijou's turn. Okay.
My question is... would I rather fight one hundred chicken-sized hippopotamuses on A...
...or one hippo-sized chicken on B? Do you understand?
No! I understand! Okay, okay.
One hundred... one hundred chicken-sized hippopotamuses! One hippo-sized chicken!
Are you sure you know? I'm not repeating it. Okay, this is actually a good one. Okay.
Ready? In...
Three, two, one!
Oh, look at them, they're on B!
I don't want to get dirty!
Bijou doesn't like ads, Bijou likes boss battles. You should've known! Boss battles!
But wait, the question was...
So 100% was bad!
Ah! Unfortunately...
...unfortunately for you!
Oh, Mococo-chan!
Here comes Nerissa!
Mercy! Mercy! Mercy!
You have one chance to ask for mercy.
Don't shoot me!
Get sullied!
I will totally sully you!
Don't look at me like this! Don't look at me, okay? No!
Fortunately for us... Goodbye!
Goodbye, Mococo!
Your turn now. She became a mermaid.
She's swimming away.
We'll never see her again.
Come back to us! Don't worry, Mococo!
Come back, Mococo-chan, we need you!
I'm at my limit now!
Fuwawa...
Okay, who's next?
Last is my turn. Which means I can't get it wrong, which feels pretty good.
What's a good question? I'm not really sure.
Let's see.
Nerissa is a demon, but she's also half raven.
If I had to pick between worlds and either be...
...just a demon or just a raven...
So demon is B...
...raven is A.
Which would I pick?
All right, yes, okay, on three, okay?
One, two, three!
A! Oh!
I knew you would never give up laying eggs!
I can't lay eggs!
That's not okay!
I just think it would be great...
...if I could have powers that aren't dependent on...
We're in this together, at least.
...something that can break, you know?
I thought being a demon is cooler, though.
It is, but...
We definitely have to think of it from Nerissa's side!
You know what's even cooler than being a demon?
You know what's even cooler than being a demon, Shiori and Mococo?
What? What? I dare you! I dare you!
Get sullied!
Yes, there you go!
Oh, I look like a cockroach now!
Yeah, you want to crawl with us?
I like baths, it's okay!
Since you like it so much, go take one in the ocean!
Go! Go!
Don't run away like this!
Well, we'll never see them again.
They're getting lost in the water.
I think they're having too much fun. They're digging up the sea!
But it's fine.
Don't eat the salt water!
Yeah, don't drink the water!
Dancing on the beach... Yeah!
I'm gonna get rid of this.
Whoa!
Oh, that was close.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think I'm...
Hey hey hey hey hey!
That didn't go so well, huh? Look how dirty you are!
But hey, idols don't give up that easy, right?
You are idols, right? Let's turn this around and shine again!
We are idols? Idols after being sullied?
And if you do... I'll take you somewhere super special—
—where even Justice can't find us!
No way! Wait, I kind of want...
I want Justice to find me at some point! What? No!
No way!
Well, you can go...
Okay, just for now! Just for now!
Yeah!
Let's go!
どこ？ そこ？ あそこ？ 見つからないぜ？
Where? There? Over there? You won't find us!
パパイヤ マンゴー ココ☆ナツ！
Papaya, mango, coconuts!
かき氷 イチゴ味
Shaved ice, strawberry flavor
ベロを出したら まっかっか！ AI！
Stick out your tongue, it's bright red! AI!
猛暑 残暑 水着SHOW！ SAY！
Extreme heat, lingering summer heat, swimsuit show! Say!
ジャジャジャジャジャジャジャーン
Ta-da-da-da-da-da-da!
ココナツ イェイ
Coconuts, yay!
カチカチに燃えてる おひさま
The sun is burning intensely hot
パシュワ ココナッツ ベイビー
Splash! Coconuts baby!
待ちわびた季節はサマーサマー
The long-awaited season is summer, summer!
パシュワ ココナッツ ベイビー
Splash! Coconuts baby!
思い切って 買っちゃった ビキニ
The bikini I took the plunge and bought...
すっごーく 照れるけど
...makes me so embarrassed,
負けらんない！
but I won't lose!
日焼け止め ココ☆ナツ フレイバー
Sunscreen with a coconut flavor
パシュワ ココナッツ ベイビー
Splash! Coconuts baby!
紫外線とココナツレーザー
UV rays and coconut lasers
パシュワ ココナッツ ベイビー
Splash! Coconuts baby!
どっきゅーん ずっきゅーん キミの視線
Bam! Boom! Your gaze...
心臓 大爆発
...makes my heart explode!
サシスセ ソコナツ ベイビー
Sa-shi-su-se, coconuts baby
ダディデュデ どこナツ？ ベイビー
Da-di-du-de, where-nuts? baby
かきくけ ココナツ ベイビー
Ka-ki-ku-ke, coconuts baby
サン！ サン！ サマータイム！
Sun, sun, summer time!
YES！
Yes!
コココ コッコ コッコッ コッ...
Co-co-co, co-co, co-co, co...
ココココ ココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co, co-co-co-co, co-co
ココココココココココ ココナツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co coconuts
ココココ ココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co, co-co-co-co, co-co
ココココココココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co coco...
ナツ
...nuts!
ココ ナツ
Coco... nuts!
ココナツ！
Coconuts!
カキ氷 メロン味
Shaved ice, melon flavor,
メロンを落としたら
if you drop the melon,
ゾンビだー！
it's a zombie!
勝負ゆかた着て 盆DANCE！ SAY！
Put on your best yukata and Bon Dance! Say!
ジャジャンジャジャジャジャジャーン
Ja-jan-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-jan!
ちょいなー ちょいなー ちょいなー ちょいなー！
Choina, choina, choina, choina!
むしむし うんざり 熱帯夜
On a muggy, annoying tropical night,
私は ココナツ べいべー
I am a coconut baby.
ココナツジュース 飲みたいな
I want to drink coconut juice,
私は ココナツ べいべー
I am a coconut baby.
長い夜で
Through the long night...
短いサマータイム
A short summer time.
やったもん勝ち！
First come, first served!
サシスセ ココナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-se coconuts baby,
ダディデュデド ココナツ べいべー
da-di-du-de-do coconuts baby,
カキクケ ココナツ べいべー
ka-ki-ku-ke coconuts baby!
サン！サン！サマータイム！
Sun! Sun! Summer time!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ココココ ココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co, co-co-co-co, co-co
ココココココココココ ココナツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co coconuts
ココココ ココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co, co-co-co-co, co-co
ココココココココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co coco...
ナツ
...nuts!
ココナツ！
Coconuts!
ファイヤー！
Fire!
ススススパーキング！
S-s-s-sparking!
リリリリレインボー！
R-r-r-rainbow!
フィーバー！
Fever!
ソイヤ ソイヤ ソイヤ ソイヤ！
Soiya, soiya, soiya, soiya!
アチアチのサマー
Hot, hot summer,
50度 210%
50 degrees, 210%!
アイス激アマ
Super sweet ice cream,
キャンプはさいたま
camping in Saitama!
サシスセ ココナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-se coconuts baby,
ダディデュデド ココナツ べいべー
da-di-du-de-do coconuts baby,
カキクケ ココナツ べいべー
ka-ki-ku-ke coconuts baby!
サン！サン！サマータイム！
Sun! Sun! Summer time!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ココココ ココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co, co-co-co-co, co-co
ココココココココココ ココナツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co coconuts
ココココ ココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co, co-co-co-co, co-co
ココココココココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co coco...
ナツ
...nuts!
ココナツ！
Coconuts!
ココココココココココ ココ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co coco...
ナツ
...nuts!
どこ？
Where?
そこ？ あそこ？ 見つからないぜ
There? Over there? Can't find it!
パパイヤ マンゴー ココナツ！
Papaya, mango, coconuts!
ナッツ！
Nuts!
Huh? Huh? What?
Are we in our hideout?
Yay! We're back! We're safe here!
Yeah, they can't find us here!
Well, unless I invite them over.
Don't invite them! "Okay, okay, okay!"
But isn't this our first time showing it...
...in 3D? "Yeah!"
Ta-da! "Look!"
Do you want to see our favorite parts?
Yeah! Of course!
Ooh, look!
Yeah, all the candles! We have a romantic atmosphere!
Yeah, so romantic!
But that's not all! My favorite is...
I have a favorite part too, you know.
If you look up there...
Whoa!
What light through yonder window breaks!
Wow, the moon is beautiful tonight!
月が綺麗ですね
The moon is beautiful, isn't it?
Well, about my favorite part...
Look behind you!
Eh? What? This collection!
It's all of my...!
It's all of my... [beep]!
Oh my god! "Wait, what?!" "What is that?!"
That's just a bunch of trinkets and stuff we've collected over the years, right?
And, and her...
Yes! "And that..."
And also...
Look! Our collars! They're right here!
And they're so cute! Wait, what's wrong?
Wait... What?
Oh! Wait! Weren't FuwaMoco wearing those?
Yeah, but they're right...
FuwaMoco?
We're here!
I hear your voices, but I do not see a body!
I think they're hiding.
No, wait, wait, wait... Dogs!
Dobermans?!
Oh, they're so cute! Wait a second...
Yeah, I hear those voices coming from... from the dogs?
I think this might be Fuwamoco?
Huh? What?
Wait, does that mean Fuwamoco have been turned into Dobermans?
Oh my God!
Yeah, you know, I think they actually look more like hellhounds like this.
No way! They're so cute!
Give them a big pet. "Yeah."
Yoshi yoshi! Good girls! You're a good girl, right?
Good girls! Good girls! You're a good girl, right?
Yeah, good girl. "Good girl."
But wait, why are they Dobermans all of a sudden? What happened?
Hahaha! Pokey! Pokey!
Hehehe! Not so fluffy and fuzzy now, hoeh!
Pokey, change them back now! We can't eat donuts like this!
THAT'S why you wanna turn back? Hmph, whatever.
I'll give you one final trial! Clear it, and I'll restore them!
Huh? Moco-chan, don't worry, we're going to get you back to normal!
Okay, everybody help us, please!
I guess we'll give you one donut for the rescue. "Eh? Just one?"
One donut? One each or...? "Share it!"
Eh? I kind of like you like this, so... "Oh, please!"
Well, Pokey, what kind of challenge are you going to give us today?
FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai!
Fuwamoco Fukuwarai?! "Eh?"
Behold, the challenge before you!
Eh? Oh! The carpet has changed! "Why do they have no faces? That's kind of scary."
Yeah, it is, but I like it. "Creepy."
Hehe, ever heard of Fukuwarai?
It's this old-school Japanese game--lemme show you how it's played.
See those two giant faces? Their face parts are all scattered around.
Oh! I see, I see. "Yeah."
Bijou and Shiori will be blindfolded and carry the face parts!
Blindfolded? Oh, nice! "Oh, yeah! Actually, that sounds like fun."
We don't have to do anything.
Big bird, with your words alone, you must guide them.
Lead them to place each piece... and restore FUWAMOCO's face!
Me? "Yeah, you."
Well, we're just going to be over here blindfolded. "Yeah, we're just going to chill. Good luck."
Okay, I'll do my best. "No pressure." "No pressure."
Good luck, you two!
You've got 5 minutes. Better make it count!
Okay, let's all say Fuwamoco together.
Or not! "Or not!"
Let's go!
All right, ladies. So, first plan of action, come on over, one on each side of me, pretty please.
Okay.
And then, I would like you to turn around. "Oh, okay."
So, I have prepared for you blindfolds.
So, I'm going to go ahead and just... "And feel free to adjust them as you'd like."
But that way...
you won't be able to see anything since I have to direct you. So, go ahead and turn back around.
Huh? I cannot see a thing.
Yes, perfect. That's exactly what we want. "Aha."
All right, and then we're going to go ahead and start placing these things. So, Fuwamoco...
My puppies! I'll do my best for you, okay?
Yeah! Do your best! "You can do it!"
Okay, and start!
Okay, so what I'm going to do is I'm going to hand you guys each a piece,
and then I'm going to tell you where to go.
Who goes first, then? "Faces?"
So you're each going to do one face. "Okay, okay."
We're going to start that way, Shiori.
Where am I? What is this?
Shiori's just grabbing. "I don't know what to grab."
Okay, so, Shiori, walk to me. Just walk to my voice.
This is really small. "No." "Yes, this way. Walk towards me."
Okay, okay. "Walk towards me." "If I accidentally grab something, I'm sorry."
Okay, grab onto this. This.
This? "Yes, yes."
Okay, don't move. "Okay." "Don't move."
Bijou, I want you to walk to the sound of my voice, okay?
Where is the sound of your voice?! "Right here."
Where is he? "Your right, your right."
Okay, just a little right. "Okay, forward."
Quickly! Okay, now come to me.
Where is you?
Where are you?
Okay, so I want you to grab this. "Oh, okay, I got it."
Okay, yes. So, pretty much where you are right now,
not you, Shiori. Okay, Shiori, come forward a little bit.
This forward, or this forward? "The forward towards me."
This forward? "Okay, that's too much, back up just a little bit."
And then I want you to move...
your right, your right.
Right? This is right. "Left!" "Left? Okay, back up."
Moco-chan, I don't know if this is going to work out.
Place it down.
I tried to be strong, but now I'm regretting that.
Place it down, Bijou.
Oh, down? "Yeah, yeah, okay."
Okay, forward a little bit.
Forward?
Okay, and then can you straighten it out?
Like this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just a little bit more.
Okay, yeah, yeah. And then can you just scoot the whole thing over to...
Scoot? Scoot it?
...the right? No, left! Left!
What about making sure they're doing the same thing?
No, other way!
Other way?
What are you doing?! Okay.
Next items, next items.
Stay right where you are.
I am here where I am. I'm here too, okay?
I got two, yeah.
I don't think this is heading...
Are we ready? Biboo!
Do you have eyes?
Yes? I want you both to walk backwards, okay?
Okay. How many steps?
Maybe straighten out a little bit.
Whoa, okay, that's definitely...
Okay, back? No, actually, you're perfect.
Biboo, you better get going. I know I'm perfect.
Place one down.
Which one?
This one? Or this one?
Go left again! Where am I going?
This one, right? No, move it over to the right.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Okay, place the other one down.
I don't want to hurt Fuwamoco like this. Move it towards me.
This way? No, where I am.
This way? Yeah, our faces have to be like this.
Okay, put it down. Perfect.
Okay, Biboo, come towards the sound of my voice.
Where is it? Over here, over here.
Forward, forward.
Okay, stop. Uh, now come this way a little bit.
Turn this way.
Okay, do you hear where I am?
Oh yes, yes.
Yeah, pretend you're in an immersive... okay. Perfect. Okay, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, now I want you to turn a little bit this way.
No, wait, this is all wrong!
But rotate your body! Rotate me!
And this is all wrong! Ah!
Okay, so now I want you to place the one in your left hand down, okay? On the ground.
Like this?
Yeah, okay. Now I want you to walk slightly in this direction. Just like crawl, walk.
You see what area I'm at? Oh yes, like an immersive game. Immersive game, Biboo.
Okay, place it down.
I placed it down! Boom!
Shiori, you're done with what? You have one minute... one more, okay.
Okay, I'm done. Yeah?
Okay. Now I'm going to do the last one.
So, Biboo, walk this way.
Walk this way.
Okay, put it down. Right there.
Wait, no, that's the wrong way! Pick it back up!
Opposite side! Okay.
Okay? Uh...
Behind you, move backwards, backwards, backwards, backwards.
Okay, down!
At least her face looks a bit better than before.
Okay. Now, walk this way.
This way? Yeah, yeah. Now walk to your left.
30 seconds left! No, no, sorry, right.
You're going to make us mess up! Sorry! This way, this way, this way.
Yes, okay, now forward.
Forward. So good.
Now put it down.
Yeah, place it down, please. Is it done?
Okay, we're done.
15 seconds left! Are you done?
And...
Thank you, work! Make a wish, make a wish!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, 15 seconds. Don't worry about it.
Oh, we're done?
3, 2, 1! Done!
Okay, I want you guys to turn on around, and we're going to take off your blindfolds so you can see how you did, okay?
Wait, which one's around? This way?
This way.
Well, let's take a look.
I thought we did great. Yeah.
There is no way we can look at it. Yeah.
Look! It's...
Pokey, what do you think? Isn't it good?
Hey, Bijou, Shiori! You sure this is Fuwawa and Mococo?
[Pokey: Hey, Bijou, Shiori! You sure this is Fuwawa and Mococo?]
Yeah, look at it.
Slightly skewed a little.
Nah, not at all.
It looks good! Don't you think?
Can we have a donut, please? No.
They're not upside down or anything.
Can we have our donuts now? I think it looks perfect. Why are you saying that?
Oh, I'm not seeing anything.
We tried to make it better!
It's perfect! It's perfect just like this.
Wait, wait, wait, let me put this over here.
I want to place it there. That's perfect!
Put it on, put it on like...
Fuwawa!
Yeah, that's great.
That's my decision, you see, to do it like this because...
...I just wanted to see what it would look like. A little lower.
This is not good.
Well, is it good enough to get changed back, Pokey?
Hmph, fine. I'll change them back!
[Pokey: Hmph, fine. I'll change them back!]
Yay!
Fuwamoco is back!
Huh? Huh?
Yeah!
Oh my god!
These arms are... Oh, they're normal.
Normal, normal.
You didn't... You didn't make my dream come true.
That's not so good! No, no, no, no, no!
It's okay, I like you better this way.
Oh, there's my face!
Whose face is this?
Whose mouth is this?
I'm really glad we could get through this together. Aren't you, guys?
Yeah!
How is our friendship?
Yeah! Friendship!
As Advent, you've gotta keep working together and looking out for one another!
Oh, yeah! Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, that's karma. Yeah, get down.
Whoa!
Checkmate, I'm a superstar
Stay insane, but you rock with it, ah
Like 24/7 I'm a hot mess, ya love-hate
Get less boring, oh my god!
ホームラン, バタバタ swing my shot
Home run, flailing, swing my shot
Oh, what-what? Ah, yeah
Like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different
派手にブチかまそう
Let's make a big splash and blow it up
ya, ya, ya
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"Chaotic good" is peak right now
I can show ya how
ya, ya, ya
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
No way, no way, yeah, way-o, way-o, yeah
"Good vs Evil" is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party
Just leave it to moi... What? Uh
Whoops, what, uh
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
Uh, that's karma, ta-da, ha ha ha
Awoof, what, uh
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it
Yeah, that's karma, ta-da, ha ha ha
Sorry I'm just better
Sorry we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever
ya, ya, ya
Whatever!
Talk about a "kumbaya"
ya, ya, ya
Hey y'all, check on this sound
フルボッコんボッちやって
Beat them to a pulp and thrash them
欲望召し上がれ
feast upon your desires
アイ、ハート、get down, ウィンク
Ai, heart, get down, wink
See yonara サイコですわ
See ya, you're a psycho
Baw baw
ドメスティック
Domestic
Baw baw, ドラマティック
Baw baw, Dramatic
愛しき人々 この指とまれ
Beloved people, gather at this finger
Hey! Yeah!
Uh-huh
ハードにハートはハイになって弾けて
Hearts turning high and bursting,
恥じらい捨てちゃえ
throw away your shyness.
叫び踊り誇れ 激動的 show 体
Shout, dance, and be proud of this passionate show-body.
酔いしれてちょーだい
Get intoxicated, come on!
道化のパラダイス
Paradise of clowns,
惹かれ合う感覚が共鳴共鳴
sensations of mutual attraction resonating, resonating.
"Good vs. Evil, but I'm which one?"
Just stuck here in the middle
That's not any fun
What, uh
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
Uh, that's karma, ta-da, ha ha ha
Awoof, what, uh
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it
Yeah, that's karma, ta-da, ha ha ha
想像から創造
From imagination to creation
衝動から猛攻
From impulse to fierce attack
ほらあっという間に華麗に変身変幻自在
Look, in the twinkling of an eye, transforming brilliantly, ever-changing.
毒々しい本能
Poisonous instinct,
喰らえ咆哮
devour the roar.
ya, ya, ya
Ah, ya, ya, ya, oh
Talk about a "kumbaya"
Sorry I'm just better
Sorry we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever
Whatever!
ya, ya, ya
Talk about a "kumbaya"
ISEKAI queen, switch tuning minor
Colorful cacophony
ya, ya, ya
歪で優雅にハチャメチャ
Distorted yet graceful, haphazardly chaotic.
Welcome to Miss Fortune's game
ya, ya, ya
Oh, yeah! Yay!
Well, that was Go-Getters!
How did you like our performance?
Yeah! Woo!
To everybody watching right now...
We all have some big news!
Big news!
And guess what? For our first anniversary, we have...
...two big announcements!
Yeah! Two!
The first one is...
A brand new song!
Yeah!
Our second original song in the story of Advent...
PRISONER!
...will be released on August 31st...
...at 12:00 AM local time in each region!
Wait, who's the prisoner? Are we the prisoner? Is someone else the prisoner?
It's just Prisoner, baby!
You guys, it's gonna sound great! Yeah!
Yeah!
If you want to find out,
don't go anywhere because you'll be redirected
to the music video right after this stream!
And guess what!
We're also ready to premiere the new song
right after this!
Alright, everybody, are you ready?
Places! Places, places!
Okay, places.
Okay.
Locked away where nightmares keep you awake,
you'll be safe within my crushing embrace.
(You're all mine, all mine)
You'll never escape...
Wayward soul, I'll wrap you up in
darkness that consumes you whole,
hold you in my labyrinth of walls.
(Lost in the depths that swallow you,
where just your shadows follow you)
Always churning in the deep, I
won't let you sleep.
You don't need your dreams now that you belong to me.
Throw them all away, you're too frail to be free.
(You will always be)
My lovely prisoner
(Are you shaking?)
My eyes will find you,
let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine)
Poor little prisoner
(Are you breaking?)
My chains will bind you here forever,
stay here for all time.
In tenebris
In frigore
In carcere
Close your eyes, go deeper in the
emptiness that plagues your mind,
let my dark envelop your light.
I will keep you safe and sound,
Hear the blissful silence all around.
I'll drag you down below,
never let you go.
Everything you've been,
the transgressions of your past;
throw them all away,
let me hold you at last.
My lovely prisoner
(What's the matter?)
You're never leaving,
you are mine forever
(Got to keep you right here)
Poor, helpless prisoner
(Did you shatter?)
Why are you grieving your ambitions?
Let them disappear.
I can hear your plea,
reaching desperately,
but I'll never, ever
set you free.
Stay with me.
My lovely prisoner
(Are you shaking?)
My eyes will find you,
let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine)
Poor little prisoner
(Are you breaking?)
My chains will bind you here forever,
stay here for all time.
In tenebris
In frigore
In carcere
Yeah!
That was our new song, 'Prisoner'!
What did you think of the track, huh?
Hot song, huh?
Yeah!
Okay, and let's all move on to the second piece of exciting news. Getting close, girls.
Hmm?
Hololive English -Advent- 1st Anniversary Celebration!
Yeah!
First up, we have...
...the Framed Art Board!
It's a large illustration board framed beautifully!
The luxurious frame features our logo with foil stamping for extra shine.
It's a perfect item to decorate your home and to enjoy looking at every single day
so you can see all of us together, just like we should be!
Yeah! Aw!
Well, next up...
...we have a Sticker Set from Halloween 2024 Version!
Woo! Yeah!
Five different designs, and it includes the chibi art design released for
Halloween plus a 3-piece sticker set
featuring each Advent member's original design!
And then you can put them on your phone, put them on your PC, and have fun with them!
Yeah! Have fun!
Alright, next up we've got...
...the Connecting Charm!
What's awesome is that all these charms can actually connect...
...to each other!
You can mix and match all kinds of different ways, right?
And have fun! -Yeah!
Finally, we've got the Varsity Jacket!
Wow!
It's got the Advent logo on the back...
...and Poki is embroidered on the front chest area, too!
Wow! Cute!
And guess what!
-What? -What?
You can actually attach those charms...
...I just showed you on the zipper of the jacket, too!
Awesome!
You know, it's a cool item that you can rock...
...both in your everyday life and at events, too!
Yeah!
Guess what!
-What? -What?
It's happening right now!
The merch just dropped at the hololive official shop!
Hey guys, notice that card showing up on the bottom of...
...the bottom-left? Left of the YouTube screen?
Go ahead and click it to shop your favorites, okay?
Click, click, click, click, click!
This was such a wonderful day together.
I had so much fun!
Even though we were running for just about half the time.
Yeah, but that's a typical Friday.
Who was really worried?
No! Better luck next time, Justice!
As if you could ever catch us!
We've been together for two years!
Yeah, can you believe it?
That's a lot of memories.
Yeah, lots of memories.
And we're looking forward to all of the next years together!
Year three, year four, year five, year six!
Yeah!
We're going to keep running!
Bye-bye! Advent!